question_data = [
    {"question": "A slug's blood is green.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, "
             "you are free to take it home to eat.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "correct_answer": "True"}
]

question_data_film = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio&#039;s character hunts down the killer of his son.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
